Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
BARTON: Okay, hold on,
don't shoot.
- You see where you're going?
- Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Now, let's worry
about how you get there.
Gotta move
your foot here.
Point your toe this way.
Your hips here.
Okay?
- Can you see?
- Yeah.
- Are you sure?
- Mm-hmm.
How about now?
Can you see now?
- (CHUCKLES) No.
- How about now?
(BOTH LAUGH)
All right.
Ready? Three fingers.
COOPER: Nice!
LAURA: Nice throw, kiddo.
COOPER: Here you go.
Hey, you guys
want mayo? Or mustard?
Or both?
Who puts mayo
on a hot dog?
Probably your brothers.
Uh, two mustard, please!
Thanks, Mama.
LAURA: Got it!
Nate, mayo or mustard?
How about ketchup?
LAURA: Or ketchup.
I got ketchup, too.
BARTON: Mind your elbow.
(LAUGHS)
Good job, hawk-eye.
Go get your arrow.
(CHUCKLES)
LAURA: Hey, guys!
Enough practice.
Soup's on!
BARTON: All right.
We're coming.
We're hungry.
Lila, let's go.
Lila?
Honey?
Hey, babe?
- (THUNDER RUMBLING)
- Babe?
Babe?
(WHISTLES) Boys!
Boys!
Laura!
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
(PSYCHEDELIC
ROCK SONG PLAYING)
- (GRUNTS)
- (OBJECT CLATTERS)
You don't need
to do that.
Because, uh, you're just
holding the position.
- Oh, yeah.
- (GRUNTS)
- That was close.
That's a goal.
We are now one apiece.
I would like to try again.
We're tied up.
Feel the tension?
It's fun.
That was terrible.
Now you have a chance to win.
And you've won.
Congratulations.
Fair game.
Good sport.
You have fun?
It was fun.
- (CLICKS)
- (GRUNTS)
(HELMET WHIRRING)
(SIGHS)
This thing on?
Hey, Miss Potts. Pep.
(EXHALES DEEPLY)
If you find this recording...
don't post it on social media.
It's gonna be
a real tearjerker.
I don't know if you're
ever gonna see these.
I don't even know
if you're still...
Oh, God, I hope so.
Today's day 21.
No, uh, 22.
You know, if it wasn't for
the existential terror...
of staring into
the literal void of space,
I'd say I'm feeling
a little better today.
Infection's run its course,
thanks to
the Blue Meanie back there.
Oh, you'd love her.
Very practical.
Only a tiny bit sadistic.
So, the fuel cells were
cracked during battle...
and we figured out a way
to reverse the ion charge...
and bought ourselves about
48 hours of flight time.
Uh, but it's now dead
in the water.
Thousand light years
from the nearest 7-Eleven.
Oxygen will run out
tomorrow morning...
and that'll be it.
Pep, I know I said
no more surprises...
but I gotta say
I was really hoping
to pull off one last one.
But it looks like...
Well, you know
what it looks like.
Don't feel bad about this.
I mean, actually, if you
grovel for a couple weeks...
and then move on
with enormous guilt...
I should probably lie down
for a minute.
Go rest my eyes.
(SIGHS)
Please know...
when I drift off, it'll be
like every night lately.
I'm fine. Totally fine.
I dream about you.
Because it's always you.
(CLICKS, POWERS OFF)
(GROANING SOFTLY)
(BREATHES DEEPLY)
(DISTANT BOOM)
(RUMBLING)
(TONY PANTING)
Couldn't stop him.
Neither could I.
Hang on.
I lost the kid.
Tony, we lost.
Is, uh...?
- Oh, good.
- Oh, my God!
Oh, my God! (SOBBING)
It's okay.
RHODES: It's been 23 days
since Thanos came to Earth.
NATASHA: World governments
are in pieces.
The parts that are
still working...
...are trying to take a census
and it looks like he did...
He did exactly what he said
he was gonna do.
Thanos wiped out...
...50% of all
living creatures.
Where is he now? Where?
We don't know.
He just opened a portal
and walked through.
(SIGHS)
What's wrong with him?
ROCKET: Oh, he's pissed.
He thinks he failed.
Which, of course, he did...
but there's a lot of that
going around, ain't there?
Honestly,
until this exact second
I thought you were
a Build-A-Bear.
Maybe I am.
We've been hunting Thanos
for three weeks now.
Deep space scans...
and satellites,
and we got nothing.
Tony, you fought him.
Who told you that?
I didn't fight him.
No, he wiped my face
with a planet...
while the Bleecker Street
magician
gave away the store.
That's what happened.
There was no fight,
'cause he's not beatable.
Did he give you any clues,
any coordinates, anything?
Uh... (SPUTTERS)
I saw this coming
a few years back.
I had a vision.
I didn't wanna believe it.
Thought I was dreaming.
Tony, I'm gonna
need you to focus.
And I needed you.
As in, past tense.
That trumps what you need.
It's too late, buddy.
Sorry.
(SNIFFS) You know what I need?
I need a shave.
And I believe I remember
telling all youse...
Tony, Tony!
...alive and otherwise,
that what we needed
was a suit of armor
around the world.
Remember that?
Whether it impacted
our precious freedoms or not.
That's what we needed.
Well, that didn't
work out, did it?
I said we'd lose.
You said, "We'll do that
together, too."
And guess what, Cap?
We lost.
And you weren't there.
But that's what
we do, right?
Our best work after the fact?
We're the "Avengers."
We're the "Avengers,"
not the "Pre-vengers."
- Okay.
- Right?
You made your point.
Just sit down, okay?
Okay. No, no, here's my point.
You know what?
- She's great by the way.
- Tony, you're sick. Sit down.
TONY: We need you.
You're new blood.
Bunch of tired old mules.
I got nothing for you, Cap.
I got no coordinates...
no clues, no strategies,
no options.
Zero. Zip. Nada.
No trust, liar.
(TONY BREATHING SHAKILY)
Here, take this.
You find him,
you put that on...
you hide.
- STEVE: Tony!
- I'm fine.
Let me...
RHODES: Bruce gave him
a sedative.
He's gonna probably be out
for the rest of the day.
CAROL: You guys
take care of him...
and I'll bring him a Xorrian
elixir when I come back.
Where are you going?
To kill Thanos.
NATASHA: Hey.
You know, we usually work
as a team here...
and, uh, between you and I,
morale's a little fragile.
We realize up there
is more your territory,
but this is
our fight, too.
You even know
where he is?
I know people who might.
NEBULA: Don't bother.
I can tell you
where Thanos is.
Thanos spent a long time
trying to perfect me.
And when he worked,
he talked about his Great Plan.
Even disassembled,
I wanted to please him.
I'd ask...
where would we go
once his plan was complete?
And his answer
was always the same.
"To the Garden."
That's cute.
Thanos has a retirement plan.
So, where is he?
When Thanos snapped
his fingers...
Earth became ground zero
for a power surge
of ridiculously
cosmic proportions.
No one's ever seen
anything like it.
Until two days ago...
on this planet.
Thanos is there.
He used the stones again.
BANNER: Hey, hey, hey.
(CHUCKLES)
We'd be going in
shorthanded, you know?
RHODES: Look, he's still
got the stones, so...
So, let's get 'em.
Use them to bring
everyone back.
BANNER: Just like that?
Yeah. Just like that.
Even if there's a small chance
that we can undo this...
I mean, we owe it to everyone
who's not in this room to try.
If we do this,
how do we know
it's gonna end any differently
than it did before?
Because before
you didn't have me.
Hey, new girl?
Everybody in this room
is about that superhero life.
And if you don't mind
my asking,
where the hell
have you been all this time?
There are a lot of other
planets in the universe.
And unfortunately,
they didn't have you guys.
(RUMBLING)
I like this one.
Let's go get
this son of a bitch.
Okay.
Who here hasn't been
to space?
- Why?
- (CAROL CHUCKLES)
You better not throw up
on my ship.
Approaching jump in three...
two, one.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
I'll head down for recon.
This is gonna work, Steve.
I know it will.
'Cause I don't know what
I'm gonna do if it doesn't.
No satellites.
No ships. No armies.
No ground defenses
of any kind.
It's just him.
And that's enough.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(POT CLANKING)
(GRUNTS)
(CHOKING)
(GRUNTING)
(SCREAMING)
(THANOS GROANING)
Oh, no.
(GROANS)
Where are they?
- (GROANING)
- Answer the question.
The universe
required correction.
After that, the stones
served no purpose...
beyond temptation.
You murdered trillions!
- You should be grateful.
- (BANNER GRUNTS)
Where are the stones?
Gone.
Reduced to atoms.
You used them two days ago!
I used the stones
to destroy the stones.
It nearly killed me.
But the work is done.
It always will be.
I am inevitable.
We have to tear this place apart.
He has to be lying!
NEBULA: My father
is many things.
A liar is not one of them.
Ah.
Thank you, daughter.
Perhaps I treated you
too harshly.
(GRUNTS)
BANNER: What?
What did you do?
I went for the head.
MAN: So...
...I, uh, went on a date
the other day.
It's the first time
in five years.
You know? I'm sitting there
at dinner.
I didn't even know
what to talk about.
What did you talk about?
Eh, same old crap. You know,
how things have changed.
My job, his job.
How much we miss the Mets.
And then things got quiet...
then he cried as they were
serving the salads.
What about you?
I cried just before dessert.
But I'm seeing him
again tomorrow, so...
That's great.
You did the hardest part.
You took the jump.
You didn't know where
you were gonna come down.
And that's it.
That's those little
brave baby steps
we gotta take...
to try and become whole again,
try and find purpose.
I went in the ice in '45,
right after I met
the love of my life.
Woke up 70 years later.
You gotta move on.
Gotta move on.
The world is in our hands.
It's left to us, guys.
And we gotta do
something with it.
Otherwise...
Thanos should've killed
all of us.
(RAT SQUEAKING)
(BEEPS)
(BEEPING)
(POWERING UP)
(GROANS)
(BLOWS)
What the hell?
(ELECTRICITY CRACKLING)
(POWERS DOWN)
Hope?
(INAUDIBLE)
Kid!
Hey, kid!
What the hell happened here?
(BIRD CAWING)
Oh, my God!
Oh, please!
Please, please!
No, no, no. No.
No.
Excuse me. Sorry.
Oh, Cassie, no.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Please, please, please.
No, Cassie.
What?
(GASPING)
Cassie?
Dad?
(SOBBING)
(SOBS)
- You're so big!
- (BOTH LAUGH)
ROCKET: (ON SPEAKERS)
Yeah. We boarded
that highly-suspect
warship Danvers pinged.
It was an infectious
garbage scow.
So, thanks
for the hot tip.
Well, you were closer.
ROCKET: Yeah. And now
we smell like garbage.
You get a reading
on those tremors?
'Twas a mild subduction
under the African plate.
Do we have a visual?
How are we handling it?
OKOYE: Nat.
It's an earthquake
under the ocean.
We handle it
by not handling it.
Carol, are we seeing you
here next month?
Not likely.
What? You gonna get
another haircut?
Listen, fur face.
I'm covering
a lot of territory.
The things that are
happening on Earth
are happening
everywhere.
On thousands of planets.
All right, all right.
That's a good point.
So, you might not see me
for a long time.
All right. Uh, well...
This channel's
always active.
So, if anything
goes sideways...
anyone's making trouble
where they shouldn't...
comes through me.
(ASSENTS IN XHOSA)
Okay.
All right.
Good luck.
(SIGHS SOFTLY)
Where are you?
RHODES: Mexico.
The Federales found
a room full of bodies.
Looks like a bunch
of cartel guys...
never even had a chance
to get their guns off.
It's probably a rival gang.
Except it isn't.
It's definitely Barton.
What he's done here...
what he's been doing
for the last few years...
I mean, the scene
that he left...
I gotta tell you,
there's a part of me that
doesn't even wanna find him.
Will you find out
where he's going next?
Nat?
Please?
Okay.
(BREATHES SHAKILY)
STEVE: You know, I'd offer
to cook you dinner...
but you seem
pretty miserable already.
NATASHA: You here
to do your laundry?
And to see a friend.
Clearly, your friend is fine.
You know,
I saw a pod of whales
when I was coming over
the bridge.
- In the Hudson?
- There's fewer ships...
cleaner water.
You know, if you're
about to tell me
to look on the bright side...
Um...
I'm about to hit you
in the head
with a peanut butter sandwich.
Hmm.
Sorry.
Force of habit.
You know,
I keep telling everybody
they should move on...
and grow.
Some do.
But not us.
If I move on, who does this?
Maybe it doesn't need
to be done.
I used to have nothing.
And then I got this.
This job.
This family.
And I was better
because of it.
And even though
they're gone...
I'm still trying to be better.
I think we both
need to get a life.
You first.
(DEVICE CHIMES)
SCOTT: (ON SPEAKERS)
Oh, hi, hi!
Uh, is anyone home?
This is, uh, Scott Lang.
We met a few years ago
at the airport...
in Germany?
I was the guy that got
really big. I had a mask on.
- You wouldn't recognize me.
- Is this an old message?
SCOTT: Ant-Man?
I know you know that.
It's the front gate.
SCOTT: I really need
to talk to you guys.
(MUTTERING TO HIMSELF)
STEVE: Scott.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Have either of you guys
ever studied quantum physics?
Only to make
conversation.
All right, so...
five years ago,
right before...
Thanos...
I was in a place called
the quantum realm.
The quantum realm is like
its own microscopic universe.
To get in there,
you have to be incredibly small.
Hope. She's my, um...
She was my...
She was supposed
to pull me out.
And then Thanos happened...
and I got stuck in there.
I'm sorry, that must have
been a very long five years.
Yeah, but that's just it.
It wasn't.
For me, it was five hours.
See, the rules
of the quantum realm
aren't like
they are up here.
Everything is unpredictable.
Is that anybody's sandwich?
I'm starving.
Scott.
What are you
talking about?
(MUFFLED) So...
what I'm saying is...
time works differently
in the quantum realm.
The only problem is
right now
we don't have a way
to navigate it.
But what if we did?
I can't stop thinking
about it.
What if we could somehow
control the chaos...
and we could navigate it?
What if there was a way...
that we could enter
the quantum realm
at a certain point in time...
but then exit
the quantum realm
at another point in time?
Like...
- Like before Thanos.
- STEVE: Wait.
Are you talking
about a time machine?
No. No, of course not.
No, not a time machine.
This is more like a...
Yeah. Like a time machine.
I know, it's crazy.
It's crazy.
(STAMMERS) But I can't stop
thinking about it.
There's gotta be...
some way... (SIGHS)
- It's crazy.
- NATASHA: Scott.
I get emails from a raccoon...
so nothing sounds crazy
anymore.
So, who do we talk to
about this?
Chow time!
Maguna.
Morgan H. Stark,
you want some lunch?
Define "lunch"
- or be disintegrated.
- Okay.
You should not be
wearing that, okay?
That is part of a special
anniversary gift
I'm making for Mom.
There you go.
You thinking about lunch?
I can give you a handful of
crickets on a bed of lettuce.
- No.
- That's what you want.
How did you find this?
- Garage.
- Really?
- Were you looking for it?
- No.
- I found it, though.
- Hmm.
You like going in
the garage, huh?
So does Daddy. (GRUNTS)
It's fine, actually.
Mom never wears anything I buy her.
So, I'm gonna...
(STAMMERS) No. We know
what it sounds like.
Tony, after everything
you've seen,
is anything really
impossible?
Quantum fluctuation messes
with the Planck scale...
which then triggers
the Deutsch Proposition.
Can we agree on that?
Thank you.
In layman's terms,
it means you're not coming home.
- I did.
- No.
You accidentally survived.
(SIGHS)
It's a billion-to-one
cosmic fluke.
And now you wanna pull a...
What do you call it?
A time heist?
Yeah, a time heist.
Of course.
Why didn't we think
of this before?
Oh, because it's laughable.
Because it's a pipe dream.
The stones are in the past.
We could go back,
we could get them.
We can snap our own fingers.
We can bring everybody back.
Or screw it up worse than
he already has, right?
I don't believe we would.
Gotta say it. I sometimes
miss that giddy optimism.
However, high hopes
won't help...
if there's no logical,
tangible way
for me to safely execute
said time heist.
I believe
the most likely outcome
will be our
collective demise.
Not if we strictly follow
the rules of time travel.
All right? It means no
talking to our past selves...
no betting
on sporting events.
I'm gonna stop you
right there, Scott.
Are you seriously
telling me
that your plan
to save the universe...
is based on
Back to the Future?
- Is it?
- No.
Good. You had me
worried there.
'Cause that would be
horseshit.
That's not how
quantum physics works.
Tony.
We have to take a stand.
We did stand.
And yet, here we are.
SCOTT: I know you got
a lot on the line.
You got a wife, a daughter.
But I lost someone
very important to me.
A lotta people did.
And now, now we have a chance
to bring her back...
to bring everyone back,
and you're telling me
that you won't even...
That's right, Scott.
I won't even.
- I can't.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
(FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING)
MORGAN STARK: Mommy told me
to come and save you.
Good job. I'm saved.
I wish you were coming here
to ask me something else.
Anything else.
I'm honestly happy
to see you guys, I just...
Oh, look, the table's
set for six.
Tony. I get it.
And I'm happy for you.
I really am.
But this is a second chance.
I got my second chance
right here, Cap.
Can't roll the dice on it.
If you don't talk shop,
you can stay for lunch.
Well, he's scared.
STEVE: He's not wrong.
SCOTT: Yeah, but, I mean,
what are we gonna do?
We need him.
What, are we gonna stop?
No, I wanna do it right.
We're gonna need
a really big brain.
Bigger than his?
Come on, I feel like I'm
the only one eating here.
Try some of that.
Have some eggs.
I'm so confused.
These are confusing times.
(CHUCKLES)
Right, no, no.
That's not what I meant.
Nah, I get it.
I'm kidding!
I know, it's crazy.
I'm wearing shirts now.
Yeah. What? How? Why?
Five years ago,
we got our asses beat.
Except it was worse
for me...
'cause I lost twice.
First, Hulk lost,
then Banner lost...
and then, we all lost.
No one blamed you, Bruce.
I did.
For years, I've been
treating the Hulk
like he's some kind
of disease...
something to get rid of.
But then, I start looking
at him as the cure.
Eighteen months
in the gamma lab.
I put the brains
and the brawn together...
and now, look at me.
Best of both worlds.
- Excuse me, Mr. Hulk?
- Yes.
Can we get a photo?
100%, little person.
Come on, step on up.
Do you mind?
- Oh, yeah, yeah.
- SMART HULK: Thanks.
Say "green."
- FANS: Green.
- Green.
Did you get that?
That's a good one.
Did you want to grab one
with me? I'm Ant-Man.
They're Hulk fans.
They don't know Ant-Man.
- Nobody does.
- No, he wants you to take
- a picture with him.
- I don't want a picture.
Stranger danger.
Yeah, look, he's even
saying no, he doesn't.
I get it.
I don't want it, either.
But come on. The kid...
I don't want a picture
with them.
- He's gonna feel bad.
- Sorry.
They're happy to do it.
They said they'll do it.
- SCOTT: I don't want to do it.
- We can do it.
- SMART HULK: No, you feel bad.
- Take the goddamn phone.
SMART HULK: Okay.
GIRL: Thank you, Mr. Hulk.
SMART HULK: No, it was great,
kids. Thank you very much.
ALL: Hulk out!
STEVE: Bruce.
Dab.
- Bruce.
- Listen to your mom.
She knows better.
About what we were saying.
Right.
The whole time travel
do-over?
Eh, guys, it's outside
of my area of expertise.
Well, you pulled this off.
I remember a time when that
seemed pretty impossible, too.
I've got a mild inspiration.
I'd like to see
if it checks out.
So, I'd like to run
one last sim
before we pack it in
for the night.
This time, in the shape
of a Mobius strip,
inverted, please.
FRIDAY: Processing.
Right, give me the eigenvalue
of that particle...
factoring in spectral decomp.
- That'll take a second.
- FRIDAY: Just a moment.
And don't worry if it doesn't pan out.
I'm just kinda...
Model rendered.
(PUFFS)
(EXHALES SHARPLY)
Shit!
MORGAN STARK: Shit!
(WHISPERS) What are you
doing up, little miss?
- Shit.
- Nope. We don't say that.
Only Mommy says that word.
She coined it.
It belongs to her.
Why are you up?
'Cause I've got some
important shit going on here!
Why do you think?
No, I got something
on my mind.
I got something on my mind.
Was it juice pops?
Sure was.
That's extortion.
That's a word.
What kind you want?
Great minds think alike.
Juice pops exactly...
was on my mind.
You done? Yeah?
Now you are.
Here. Wipe.
Good. That face
goes there.
Tell me a story.
A story.
Once upon a time, Maguna went to bed.
The end.
That is a horrible story.
Come on, that's
your favorite story.
Love you tons.
I love you 3,000.
Wow.
(WHISPERS) 3,000.
That's crazy.
Go to bed or I'll sell
all your toys.
- Night night.
- (DOOR CLOSES)
Not that it's a competition...
but she loves me 3,000.
Does she, now?
You were somewhere
in the low 6 to 900 range.
(CHUCKLES)
Whatcha reading?
Just a book on composting.
What's new with composting?
- Interesting science...
- I figured it out.
By the way.
And, you know,
just so we're talking
about the same thing...
Time travel.
What?
Wow.
That's amazing...
and terrifying.
That's right.
(SIGHS)
We got really lucky.
Yeah.
I know.
A lot of people didn't.
Nope. And I can't
help everybody.
Sorta seems like you can.
Not if I stop.
I can put a pin in it
right now and stop.
Tony...
trying to get you to stop...
has been one of the few
failures of my entire life.
Something tells me...
I should put it
in a lockbox
and drop it to the bottom
of the lake...
and go to bed.
But would you be able to rest?
SMART HULK: Okay, here we go.
Time travel test number one.
Scott, fire up...
the, uh, van thing.
STEVE: Breakers are set.
Emergency generators
are on standby.
Good, because
if we blow the grid,
I don't want to lose, uh,
Tiny here in the 1950s.
- Excuse me?
- He's kidding.
You can't say things
like that.
(STAMMERS)
It was a bad joke.
You were kidding, right?
I have no idea.
We're talking about time travel here.
Either it's all a joke,
or none of it is.
We're good!
Get your helmet on.
Scott, I'm gonna
send you back a week...
let you walk around
for an hour,
then bring you back
in 10 seconds.
Make sense?
Perfectly not confusing.
Good luck, Scott.
You got this.
You're right.
I do, Captain America.
On a count of three...
Three, two, one.
(MACHINE WHIRS)
Uh... Guys?
This doesn't feel right.
STEVE: What is this?
- What's going on?
- NATASHA: Who is that?
- Hold on.
- Is that Scott?
Yes, it's Scott.
- What's going on, Bruce?
- Oh, my back!
- What is this?
- Hold on a second.
Could I get
a little space here?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can you bring him back?
I'm working on it.
(BEEPING)
It's a baby.
- It's Scott.
- STEVE: As a baby.
- SMART HULK: He'll grow.
- Bring Scott back.
When I say kill the power,
kill the power.
Oh, my God.
And... kill it!
Somebody peed my pants.
Oh, thank God.
But I don't know
if it was baby me or old me.
Or just me me.
Time travel!
What?
I see this as an absolute win.
- (TIRES SQUEALING)
- (ENGINE ROARING)
Why the long face?
Let me guess,
he turned into a baby.
Among other things, yeah.
What are you doing here?
It's the EPR Paradox.
Instead of pushing Lang
through time,
you might've wound up...
pushing time through Lang.
It's tricky, dangerous.
Somebody could have
cautioned you against it.
You did.
Oh, did I?
Well, thank God
I'm here.
Regardless, I fixed it.
A fully functioning
time-space GPS.
I just want peace.
Turns out resentment
is corrosive, and I hate it.
Me, too.
We got a shot
at getting these stones,
but I gotta tell you
my priorities.
Bring back what we lost,
I hope, yes.
Keep what I found,
I have to, at all costs.
And maybe not die trying.
Would be nice.
Sounds like a deal.
(SIGHS)
Tony, I don't know.
Why?
He made it for you.
Plus, honestly,
I have to get it out of the garage
before Morgan
takes it sledding.
Thank you, Tony.
Will you keep that
a little quiet?
Didn't bring one
for the whole team.
We are getting
the whole team, yeah?
We're working
on that right now.
(SPACESHIP ENGINE HUMMING)
ROCKET: Hey, Humie.
Where's Big Green?
The kitchen, I think.
That's awesome.
Rhodey,
careful on re-entry.
There's an idiot
in the landing zone.
Oh, God.
WAR MACHINE: What's up,
Regular-Sized Man?
(CALYPSO ROCK SONG PLAYING)
ROCKET: Kind of a step down
from the golden palaces
and the magic hammers
and whatnot.
Hey, have a little
compassion, pal.
First, they lost Asgard,
then half their people.
They're probably just happy
to have a home.
You shouldn't have come.
Ah!
Valkyrie!
Great to see you,
angry girl!
I think I liked you better
either of the other ways.
This is Rocket.
How ya doing?
He won't see you.
It's that bad, huh?
We only see him
once a month
when he comes
in for "supplies."
It's that bad.
Yeah.
(DOOR CREAKS)
What the...?
- (SNIFFS)
- (FLOORBOARD CREAKING)
Whew! Something died in here!
- (BOTTLES CLINK)
- SMART HULK: Hello? Thor!
THOR: Are you here
about the cable?
The Cinemax went out
two weeks ago...
and the sports are all
kinda fuzzy and whatnot.
SMART HULK: Thor?
(LAUGHING)
Boys! Oh, my God!
Oh, my God,
it's so good to see you!
Come here,
cuddly little rascal.
- Yeah, no, I'm good. I'm good.
- (THOR MOANS AND LAUGHS)
That's not necessary.
Hulk, you know my friends
Miek and Korg, right?
- Hey, boys!
- SMART HULK: Hey, guys.
Long time no see.
Beer's in the bucket.
Feel free to log on
to the Wi-Fi.
No password, obviously.
Thor, he's back.
That kid on the TV just
called me a dickhead again.
Noobmaster.
KORG: Yeah, NoobMaster69
called me a dickhead.
I am sick of this.
Noobmaster, hey,
it's Thor again.
You know,
the God of Thunder.
Listen, bud, if you don't log
off this game immediately...
I am gonna fly over
to your house,
come down to that basement
you're hiding in...
rip off your arms,
and shove them up your butt!
Oh, that's right, yes!
Go cry to your father,
you little weasel.
Thank you, Thor.
Let me know if he
bothers you again, okay?
Thank you very much.
I will.
So, you guys want a drink?
What are we drinking?
I've got beer, tequila,
all sorts of things.
(CHUCKLES)
SMART HULK: Buddy.
- You all right?
- Yes, I'm fine. Why?
Why, don't I look all right?
You look like
melted ice cream.
(LAUGHS)
So, what's up?
You just here for a hang, or what?
- We need your help.
- Mm.
There might be a chance
we could fix everything.
What, like the cable?
(BURPS) 'Cause that's been
driving me bananas for weeks.
Like Thanos.
Don't say that name.
Um, yeah, we don't actually
say that name in here.
SMART HULK: Please take
your hand off me.
Now, I know that guy...
might scare you.
Why would I be...?
(SCOFFS)
Why would I be scared
of that guy?
I'm the one who killed
that guy, remember?
Hmm.
Anyone else here
kill that guy?
Nope.
Didn't think so.
Korg, why don't you,
uh, tell everybody
who chopped
Thanos' big head off?
Um, Stormbreaker?
THOR: Who was swinging
Stormbreaker?
I get it. You're in
a rough spot, okay?
I've been there myself.
And you want to know
who helped me out of it?
(SLURRING) Was it Natasha?
It was you.
You helped me.
So, why don't you ask...
the Asgardians down there...
how much my help is worth?
The ones that are left,
anyway.
I think we could
bring them back.
(CHUCKLES) Stop.
Stop, okay? (SNIFFS)
I know you think I'm down here
wallowing in my own
self-pity...
waiting to be rescued
and saved...
but I'm fine, okay.
We're fine, aren't we?
Oh, we're
good here, mate.
So, whatever it is that you're
offering, we're not into it.
Don't care.
Couldn't care less.
Goodbye.
(CHUCKLES)
SMART HULK: We need you, pal.
(SNIFFS)
(CHUCKLES QUIETLY)
There's beer on the ship.
(BOTTLE CLATTERS)
What kind?
(MAN SHOUTS IN JAPANESE)
- (GRUNTS)
- (GROANS)
(MAN SHOUTS IN JAPANESE)
(GROANS)
(GUNFIRE)
(GRUNTS)
(SCOFFS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(SHOUTS IN JAPANESE)
(YELLS)
(GAGGING)
(IN ENGLISH) What I
want you can't give me.
You shouldn't be here.
Neither should you.
I've got a job to do.
NATASHA: Is that what
you're calling this?
Killing all these people
isn't gonna bring
your family back.
We found something.
A chance, maybe.
(SIGHS) Don't.
Don't what?
Don't give me hope.
I'm sorry I couldn't
give it to you sooner.
(ROCK AND ROLL SONG PLAYING)
You're drifting left.
One side there, Lebowski.
Ratchet, how's it going?
It's Rocket.
Take it easy. You're only
a genius on Earth, pal.
(THOR BELCHES)
RHODES: Time travel suit,
not bad.
Hey, hey, hey!
Easy! Easy!
I'm being very careful.
No, you're being very Hulky.
I'm being careful.
These are Pym Particles,
all right?
And ever since
Hank Pym got snapped
out of existence,
this is it.
This is what we have.
We're not making any more.
- Scott, calm down.
- SCOTT: Sorry.
We've got enough for one
round-trip each. That's it.
No do-overs.
Plus two test runs.
- (SUIT FASTENING)
- (YELLS)
One test run.
(SIGHS)
All right.
I'm not ready for this.
BARTON: I'm game.
I'll do it.
SMART HULK: Clint,
now you're gonna feel
a little discombobulated
from the chronoshift.
Don't worry about that.
RHODES: Wait a second.
Let me ask you something.
If we can do this,
you know...
go back in time, why don't
we just find baby Thanos?
You know, and...
First of all,
that's horrible.
It's Thanos.
And secondly,
time doesn't work that way.
Changing the past
doesn't change the future.
Look, we go back,
we get the stones
before Thanos gets them...
Thanos doesn't have
the stones. Problem solved.
- Bingo.
- That's not how it works.
Well, that's what
I heard.
Wait, but who?
Who told you that?
Star Trek,
Terminator, Timecop...
- Time After Time.
- Quantum Leap.
Wrinkle in Time,
Somewhere in Time.
Hot Tub Time Machine.
Bill and Ted's
Excellent Adventure.
Basically, any movie
that deals with time travel.
Die Hard.
No, that's not one.
This is known.
I don't know why
everyone believes that,
but that isn't true.
Think about it.
If you travel to the past...
that past becomes
your future...
and your former present
becomes the past...
which can't now be changed
by your new future.
Exactly.
So Back to the Future
is a bunch of bullshit?
- All right, Clint.
- (BEEPING)
We're going in three, two...
one.
(GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
(PANTING)
(GASPS)
(CONTINUES PANTING)
LILA: Cooper?
Where are my headphones?
Lila?
- COOPER: I never had them.
- Lila?
(BEEPING)
LILA: Yeah,
you had them yesterday!
Lila! Lila!
Yeah, Dad?
Dad?
Lila!
(GRUNTING)
Hey. Hey, look at me.
You okay?
Yeah. Yeah.
(PANTING)
It worked.
STEVE: Okay, so the how works.
Now, we gotta figure out
the when and the where.
Almost everyone in this room
has had an encounter...
with at least one
of the six Infinity Stones.
Or substitute
the word "encounter"...
for "damn near been killed"
by one of the six
Infinity Stones.
Well, I haven't...
but I don't even know
what the hell
you're all talking about.
Regardless, we only have
enough Pym Particles
for one round-trip each.
And these stones have been
in a lot of different places
throughout history.
Our history.
So, not a lot of convenient
spots to just drop in, yeah?
Which means we have
to pick our targets.
Correct.
So, let's start
with the Aether.
Thor, what do you know?
NATASHA: Is he asleep?
RHODES: No, no.
I'm pretty sure he's dead.
Uh, where to start? Um...
The Aether, firstly,
is not a stone.
Someone called it
a stone before.
Um, it's more of an angry
sludge sort of a thing...
so someone's gonna need
to amend that
and stop saying that.
Here's an interesting story,
though, about the Aether.
My grandfather,
many years ago...
had to hide the stone
from the Dark Elves.
Ooh. (CHUCKLES)
Scary beings.
So, Jane, actually...
Oh, there she is.
Yeah, so Jane was
an old flame of mine.
You know, she stuck her hand
inside a rock this one time...
and then the Aether
stuck itself inside her...
and she became
very, very sick.
And so I had to
take her to Asgard,
which is where I'm from...
and we had to try
and fix her.
We were dating at the time,
you see...
and I got to introduce her
to my mother...
(SIGHS) who's dead and, um...
Oh, you know, Jane and I
aren't even
dating anymore, so...
(MOUTHING)
Yes, these things happen,
though. You know?
Nothing lasts forever.
The only thing that...
- Why don't you come sit down?
- I'm not done yet.
The only thing
that is permanent in life
is impermanence. (LAUGHS)
Awesome.
Eggs? Breakfast?
No. I'd like a Bloody Mary.
ROCKET: Quill said he stole
the Power Stone from Morag.
- SMART HULK: Is that a person?
- No, Morag's a planet.
Quill was a person.
Like a planet?
Like in outer space?
Oh, look.
It's like a little puppy,
all happy and everything.
Do you wanna go to space?
You wanna go to space, puppy?
I'll take you to space.
NEBULA: Thanos found
the Soul Stone on Vormir.
What is Vormir?
NEBULA: A dominion of death...
at the very center
of celestial existence.
It's where Thanos
murdered my sister.
(STEVE SIGHS)
Not it.
- NATASHA: That Time Stone guy.
- SMART HULK: Doctor Strange.
NATASHA: Yeah, what kind
of doctor was he?
TONY: Ear-nose-throat
meets rabbit-from-hat.
SMART HULK: Nice place
in the Village, though.
TONY: Yeah,
on Sullivan Street?
SMART HULK:
Mm... Bleecker Street.
Wait, he lived
in New York?
TONY: No,
he lived in Toronto.
Uh, yeah, on Bleecker
and Sullivan.
Have you been listening
to anything?
Guys.
If you pick
the right year,
there are three stones
in New York.
Shut the front door.
STEVE: All right.
We have a plan.
Six stones, three teams,
one shot.
STEVE: Five years ago,
we lost.
All of us.
We lost friends.
We lost family.
We lost a part of ourselves.
Today, we have a chance
to take it all back.
You know your teams.
You know your missions.
Get the stones.
Get them back.
One round-trip each.
No mistakes...
no do-overs.
Most of us are going
somewhere we know.
That doesn't mean
we should know what to expect.
Be careful.
Look out for each other.
This is the fight
of our lives...
and we're gonna win.
Whatever it takes.
Good luck.
He's pretty good at that.
- Right?
- TONY: All right.
You heard the man.
Stroke those keys,
Jolly Green.
SMART HULK: Trackers engaged.
You promise to bring that
back in one piece, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, I'll do my best.
As promises go,
that was pretty lame.
- (BEEPING)
- See ya in a minute.
(CHITAURI SNARLING)
(ROARS)
(ROARING)
All right, we all have
our assignments.
Two stones uptown,
one stone down.
Stay low. Keep an eye
on the clock.
(THUD)
(ROARING)
Maybe smash a few things
along the way.
I think it's gratuitous,
but whatever.
(ROARING SOFTLY)
(ROARS SOFTLY)
ANCIENT ONE: I'd be careful
going that way.
We just had
the floors waxed.
Yeah, I'm looking
for Doctor Strange.
You're about
five years too early.
Stephen Strange is currently
performing surgery
about 20 blocks that way.
What do you want from him?
That, actually.
Ah!
I'm afraid not.
Sorry, but I wasn't asking.
You don't want
to do this.
Ah, you're right, I don't.
But I need that stone...
and I don't have time
to debate it.
(GRUNTS)
Let's start over, shall we?
ASGARDIAN MAIDEN:
For you, Lady Jane.
JANE: Um, so you have
anything with pants?
ASGARDIAN MAIDEN: Pants?
JANE: Never mind.
These will be fine. Thank you.
- ASGARDIAN MAIDEN: Yes, milady.
- THOR: Oh, there's Jane.
All right.
Here's the deal, tubby.
You're gonna charm her,
and I'm gonna poke her
with this thing...
and extract the Reality Stone,
and get gone lickety-split.
(SNIFFS)
I'll be right back, okay?
The wine cellar
is just down here.
My father used to have this
huge barrel of Aakonian ale.
I'll see if the scullery
has a couple of to-go cups.
Hey. Hey! Aren't you
drunk enough already?
(DOOR OPENS AND CLOSES)
If you could send Loki
some soup.
Yes, milady.
And ask our librarians
to pull some volumes
from the astronomy shelf.
Who's the fancy broad?
That's my mother.
She dies today.
Oh, that is today?
(BREATHES HEAVILY)
I can't do this.
I shouldn't be here.
I shouldn't have come.
It's a bad idea!
- Come here.
- No, no, no.
I think I'm having
a panic attack.
Come here. Right here.
I shouldn't be here.
This is bad.
You think you're the
only one who lost people?
What do you think
we're doing here?
I lost the only family
I ever had.
Quill, Groot, Drax,
the chick with the antenna...
all gone.
I get you miss
your mom...
but she's gone.
Really gone.
And there are plenty of people
who are only kind of gone...
and you can help them.
So, is it too much to ask
that you brush the crumbs
out of your beard...
make schmoopy talk
to Pretty Pants...
and when she's not looking,
suck out the Infinity Stone...
and help me
get my family back?
(SIGHS) Okay.
Are you crying?
(SOBBING) No.
Yes.
I feel like
I'm losing it.
Get it together!
You can do this.
(EXHALES)
(TAKING DEEP BREATHS)
All right?
Yes, I can.
Good.
I can do this. I can do this.
I can't do this.
All right, heartbreaker,
she's alone.
This is our shot.
Thor? Thor!
(GROANS)
WAR MACHINE: All right,
bring it down, Blue.
Right on that line.
That's it. Down, down.
(SNARLS)
(SIGHS)
Hey, can we hurry it up?
Guys, chop-chop. Come on.
We're on the clock.
All that is really helpful.
- Take care, okay?
- Yeah.
Get that stone and come back.
No messing around.
- Hey.
- We got this.
- Let's get it done.
- Yes, sir.
I'll see you back.
You guys watch
each other's six.
Yeah.
NEBULA: Coordinates
for Vormir are laid in.
All they have to do
is not fall out.
We're a long way
from Budapest.
(CHUCKLES)
Okay, so, uh...
we just wait around for
this Quill guy to show up...
and then he leads us to the Power
Stone, is that it?
Let's take cover.
We're not the only ones in
2014 looking for the stones.
Wait a minute.
What are you talking about right now?
Who else is looking
for these stones?
My father...
my sister...
and me.
And you?
Where are you right now?
(YELLING)
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTING)
(YELLING)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
GAMORA: You're welcome.
I didn't ask for your help.
And yet, you always need it.
- (SIGHS)
- (CHUCKLES)
Get up. Father wants us
back on the ship.
Why?
He's found an Infinity Stone.
2014 NEBULA: Where?
GAMORA: On a planet
called Morag.
Father's plan
is finally in motion.
One stone isn't six, Nebula.
It's a start.
If he gets all of them...
(THUD)
Ronan's located
the Power Stone.
I'm dispatching you
to his ship.
He won't like that.
His alternative is death.
Ronan's obsession...
clouds his judgment.
We will not fail you, Father.
No, you won't.
I swear...
I will make you proud.
(GROANING)
...we just wait around for
this Quill guy to show up...
and then he leads us to the
Power Stone, is that it?
NEBULA: Let's take cover.
We're not the only ones
in 2014
looking for the stones.
(GRUNTS)
Who was that?
I don't know.
(GASPING)
My head is splitting.
I don't know.
Her synaptic drive was
probably damaged in battle.
Shh.
Bring her to my ship.
IRON MAN:
Better hustle, Cap.
Things look like they're
just about wrapped up here.
CAPTAIN AMERICA: Got it.
I'm approaching the elevator now.
LOKI: If it's all
the same to you...
I'll have
that drink now.
2012 IRON MAN: All right,
get him on his feet.
We can all stand around
posing up a storm later.
By the way, feel free
to clean up.
(SCOFFS) Mr. Rogers,
I almost forgot that that suit...
did nothing for your ass.
CAPTAIN AMERICA: No one
asked you to look, Tony.
It's ridiculous.
ANT-MAN: I think
you look great, Cap.
As far as I'm concerned,
that's America's ass.
2012 BLACK WIDOW: Who gets
the, uh, magic wand?
2012 CAPTAIN AMERICA:
S.T.R.I.K.E. team's
- coming to secure it.
- (ELEVATOR BEEPS)
SITWELL: We can take that
off your hands.
By all means.
Careful with that thing.
Yeah, unless you want
your mind erased.
And not in a fun way.
We promise to be careful.
ANT-MAN: (ON SPEAKERS)
Who are these guys?
They are S.H.I.E.L.D.
Well, actually Hydra,
but we didn't know that yet.
ANT-MAN: Seriously?
You didn't?
I mean, they look
like bad guys.
You're small,
but you're talking loud.
On my way down to coordinate
search and rescue.
I mean, honestly,
how do you keep your food down?
Shut up.
Ooh. All right, you're up,
little buddy.
There's our stone.
ANT-MAN: All right.
Flick me.
- Move.
- Hey.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa!
- Hey, hey. Buddy!
What do you think?
Maximum occupancy has been reached.
- (GROWLS)
- Take the stairs.
2012 TONY: Yeah. Stop, stop.
(ROARS)
"Take the stairs."
Hate the stairs. (GRUNTS)
All right, Cap, I got
our scepter in the elevator...
just passing the 80th floor.
On it.
Head to the lobby.
IRON MAN: All right,
I'll see you there.
SITWELL: Evidence secure.
We're en route
to Doctor List.
No. No hitches at all,
Mr. Secretary.
Captain.
I thought
you were coordinating
search and rescue.
CAPTAIN AMERICA:
Change of plans.
Hey, Cap.
Rumlow.
I just got a call
from the secretary.
I'm gonna be running point
on the scepter.
Sir? I don't understand.
We got word there may be
an attempt to steal it.
Sorry, Cap.
We can't give you
the scepter.
I'm gonna have to call
the director.
That's okay. Trust me.
Hail Hydra.
(ELEVATOR BEEPS)
(GROANS)
So many stairs!
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
(INDISTINCT CHATTER)
Thumbelina, do you copy?
I've got eyes on the prize.
It is go time.
ANT-MAN: (ON SPEAKERS)
Bombs away.
(ANT-MAN GRUNTS)
Is that Axe Body Spray?
Yeah, I had a can in the desk
for emergencies. Relax.
Can we focus, please?
ANT-MAN:
I'm going inside you...
now.
Uh, may I ask you
where you're going?
Bit of lunch and then Asgard.
I'm sorry, you are...?
Alexander Pierce.
He's the man
above the folks
- behind Nick Fury.
- Oh.
My friends call me
Mr. Secretary.
I'm gonna have to ask you
to turn that prisoner
over to me.
Uh, Loki will be answering
to Odin himself.
PIERCE: No, he's going
to answer to us.
Odin can have what's left.
And I'm gonna need
that case.
That's been S.H.I.E.L.D.
property for over 70 years.
Hand over the case, Stark.
(INHALES SHARPLY) All right,
move it, Stuart Little.
Things are getting dicey
out here. Let's go.
I'm not gonna argue who's got
the higher authority here...
ANT-MAN: You promise me
you won't die?
We're only giving me
a mild cardiac dysrhythmia.
ANT-MAN:
That doesn't sound mild.
I need the case.
I know you got a lot of
pull, I'm just saying,
- jurisdiction...
- Okay, then give me the case.
2012 TONY:
Well, jurisdiction...
AGENT: Hand it over.
Do it, Lang!
Get your hands off me.
Window's closing.
Pull my pin.
ANT-MAN: Here goes!
(GASPING AND CHOKING)
- Stark?
- 2012 THOR: Stark?
AGENT: He's convulsing.
Give him air!
- Medic!
Give these guys
some help.
- 2012 THOR: Speak to me.
- (GASPING)
(STAMMERS) Stark,
is it your chest machine?
Breathe, breathe.
TONY: Good job.
Meet me in the alley.
I'm gonna grab
a quick slice.
(HULK ROARS)
No stairs!
(PEOPLE SCREAMING)
Uh... Come on, Stark,
stay with us.
I'm going to
try something. Okay?
I have no idea
if it's going to work.
- (GRUNTS, EXHALES)
- Yes!
Oh, that worked a treat.
Dude, that was so crazy.
I had no idea
if that was gonna work.
- The case.
- The case is, uh...
Where's the case?
Where's Loki?
Loki!
ANT-MAN: That wasn't
supposed to happen, was it?
Oh, we blew it.
Loki?
(ALARM BLARING)
Tony, what's going on?
Tell me you found that Cube.
(SIGHS)
Oh, you gotta be
shitting me.
I have eyes on Loki.
14th floor.
I'm not Loki...
and I don't wanna
hurt you.
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(PANTS)
I can do this all day.
Yeah, I know.
I know.
(BOTH GRUNT)
(PANTS)
(PANTING)
Where did you get this?
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Bucky is alive.
(COUGHS)
What?
(PANTING)
That is America's ass.
BANNER: Please, please.
I'm sorry,
I can't help you, Bruce.
If I give up
the Time Stone
to help your reality,
I'm dooming my own.
With all due respect,
all right...
I'm not sure the science
really supports that.
The Infinity Stones create
what you experience
as the flow of time.
Remove one of the stones...
and that flow splits.
Now, this may benefit
your reality...
but my new one,
not so much.
In this new branch reality...
without our chief weapon
against the forces
of darkness...
our world would be overrun.
Millions will suffer.
So, tell me, Doctor.
Can your science
prevent all that?
No...
but we can erase it.
Because once we're done
with the stones...
we can return each one
to its own timeline...
at the moment it was taken.
So, chronologically...
in that reality...
it never left.
Yes, but you're leaving out
the most important part.
In order to return the stones,
you have to survive.
We will. I will.
I promise.
I can't risk this reality
on a promise.
It's the duty
of the Sorcerer Supreme
to protect the Time Stone.
Then why the hell
did Strange give it away?
What did you say?
Strange. He gave it away.
He gave it to Thanos.
- Willingly?
- Yes.
- Why?
- I have no idea.
Maybe he made a mistake.
Or I did.
Strange is meant to be
the best of us.
So, he must've done it
for a reason.
I fear you might be right.
(SMART HULK SIGHS)
Thank you.
I'm counting on you, Bruce.
We all are.
Run diagnostics.
Show me her memory file.
Sire, the file
appears entangled.
It was a memory,
but not hers.
There's another
consciousness...
sharing her network.
Another Nebula.
Impossible.
EBONY MAW: This duplicate
carries a time stamp...
from nine years
in the future.
Where is this other Nebula?
EBONY MAW: In our
solar system on Morag.
Can you access her?
EBONY MAW: Yes,
the two are linked.
Search the duplicate's
memories...
for Infinity Stones.
BANNER:
And these stones have been
in a lot of different places
throughout history.
Our history.
So, not a lot
of convenient spots
to just drop in.
BARTON: Which means
we have to pick our targets.
- TONY: Correct.
- THANOS: Freeze image.
GAMORA: Terrans.
Avengers.
Unruly wretches.
What's that reflection?
Amplify this, Maw.
GAMORA: I don't understand.
Two Nebulas.
THANOS: No.
The same Nebula...
from two different times.
Set course for Morag.
And scan
the duplicate's memories.
I wanna see everything.
My ladies,
I'll see you after.
Go on ahead.
What are you doing?
- (THOR SCREAMS)
- (SHRIEKS)
- (GASPS)
- FRIGGA: Oh, God!
You're better off leaving
the sneaking to your brother.
No, I wasn't sneaking.
I was just going for a walk.
What are you wearing?
I always wear this.
It's one of my favorites.
(CLEARS THROAT)
THOR: Mm...
What's wrong
with your eye?
Oh, my eye.
Remember the, uh,
Battle of Harokin...
when I got hit
in the face
with the broadsword?
(CHUCKLES)
You're not the Thor
I know at all, are you?
Yes, I am.
The future hasn't been kind
to you, has it?
I didn't say
I was from the future.
I was raised by witches, boy.
I see with more than eyes,
you know that.
(VOICE BREAKING) Yeah,
I'm totally from the future.
Yes, you are, honey.
I really need
to talk to you.
We can talk.
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
His head was over there...
and his body over there...
(SCOFFS) I mean, what was
the point? I was too late.
I was just standing there.
Some idiot with an axe.
FRIGGA: Now,
you're no idiot.
You're here, aren't you?
Seeking counsel from
the wisest person in Asgard.
I am. Yes.
FRIGGA: Idiot, no.
A failure?
Absolutely.
That's a little bit harsh.
Do you know
what that makes you?
Just like everyone else.
I'm not supposed to be
like everyone else, am I?
FRIGGA: Mm.
Everyone fails at who
they're supposed to be, Thor.
The measure of a person,
of a hero...
is how well they succeed
at being who they are.
I've really
missed you, Mom.
Thor! I got it!
ASGARDIAN GUARD:
Get that rabbit!
Mom, I have to
tell you something.
No, son, you don't.
You're here to repair
your future, not mine.
This is about your future.
Uh, it's none of
my business.
- (LOUD THUD)
- (ROCKET PANTING)
Hi.
You must be Mom.
I got the thing.
Come on. We gotta move.
Oh, I wish
we had more time.
No, this was a gift.
Now you go and be the man
you're meant to be.
I love you, Mom.
I love you.
And eat a salad.
Come on, we gotta go.
- Goodbye.
- ROCKET: Three...
- Two...
- No, wait!
What am I looking at?
Oh, sometimes
it takes a second.
(GRUNTS)
(LAUGHS)
(PANTING) I'm still worthy.
Oh, boy.
- Goodbye, Mom.
- (MOUTHS) Goodbye.
('70s FUNK ROCK SONG PLAYING)
(LIP-SYNCING TO SONG)
(SCREECHES)
(QUILL SINGING ALONG
TO SONG)
So, he's an idiot?
Yeah.
RHODES: What's that?
The tool of a thief.
RHODES: Whoa, whoa, whoa.
This is the part
where spikes come out...
with skeletons on the end
of them and everything.
What are you
talking about?
When you break into
a place called
"The Temple
of the Power Stone"...
there's gonna be
a bunch of booby traps.
- Oh, my God.
- Okay. All right. Go ahead.
(BLOWS)
I wasn't always like this.
Me either.
But we work
with what we got, right?
Hmm.
Let's sync up.
Three, two, one.
(GRUNTING)
(GROANING)
(SCREAMING)
BANNER:
You murdered trillions!
THANOS:
You should be grateful.
(BANNER GRUNTS)
NATASHA:
Where are the stones?
Gone.
Reduced to atoms.
BANNER: You used them
two days ago!
I used the stones
to destroy the stones.
It nearly killed me.
But the work is done.
It always will be.
I am inevitable.
What did you do
to them?
Nothing.
Yet.
They're not trying
to stop something
I'm going to do
in our time.
They're trying
to undo something
I've already done
in theirs.
The stones.
I found them all.
I won.
Tipped the cosmic scales
to balance.
This is your future.
It's my destiny.
NEBULA:
My father is many things.
A liar is not one of them.
Ah.
Thank you, daughter.
Perhaps I treated you
too harshly.
(THOR GRUNTS)
And that is
destiny fulfilled.
Sire...
your daughter...
(CHOKING)
NEBULA: No!
...is a traitor.
That's not me.
It's not, I could never...
I would never betray you.
Never. Never.
THANOS: I know.
And you'll have the chance
to prove it.
(MOANS)
No!
He knows!
Barton! Barton, come in.
Romanoff!
Come in, we have a problem.
Come on!
Come in, we have a...
Thanos knows.
Thanos...
TONY: Cap.
Sorry, buddy,
we got a problem.
(SCOFFS)
Yeah, we do.
STEVE: Well,
what are we gonna do now?
TONY: You know what?
Give me a break, Steve.
I just got hit in the head
with the Hulk.
(SCOFFS) You said
that we had one shot.
This was our shot.
We shot it. It's shot.
Six stones or nothing.
- It was six stones or nothing.
- You're repeating yourself,
you know that?
You're repeating yourself.
Dude. Come on!
No. You never wanted
a time heist.
You weren't on board
with the time heist.
- I dropped the ball.
- You ruined the time heist.
- TONY: Is that what I did?
- SCOTT: Yeah.
Are there any other options
with the Tesseract?
No, no, no, there's
no other options.
There's no do-overs.
We're not going anywhere else.
We have one particle left.
Each.
That's it. All right?
We use that...
bye-bye,
you're not going home.
Yeah, well,
if we don't try...
then no one else
is going home, either.
I got it.
There's another way
to retake the Tesseract
and acquire new particles.
Little stroll down
memory lane.
Military installation,
Garden State.
When were they both there?
They were there at a time...
I have a vaguely exact idea.
- How vague?
- SCOTT: What are you talking about?
Where are we going?
TONY: I know for a fact
they were there.
Who's they?
What are we doing?
And I know how I know.
SCOTT: Guys, what is it?
Looks like
we're improvising.
- Great.
- What are we improvising?
Scott, get this back
to the compound.
TONY: Suit up.
- What's in New Jersey?
- TONY: 0-4.
0-4.
- TONY: Uh, 0-7.
- 0-7.
- Excuse me.
- 1-9-7-0.
Are you sure?
SCOTT: Cap? Captain?
Steve? Sorry.
America. Rogers.
Look, if you do this...
and it doesn't work,
you're not coming back.
Thanks for the pep talk,
pissant.
You trust me?
I do.
Your call.
Here we go.
('70s ROCK SONG PLAYING)
Hey, man!
Make love, not war.
TONY: Clearly you weren't
actually born here, right?
STEVE: The idea of me was.
TONY: Right. Well,
imagine you're S.H.I.E.L.D...
running a quasi-fascistic
intelligence organization...
where do you hide it?
In plain sight.
(VISOR TRILLS)
(ELEVATOR BELL DINGS)
Good luck
on your mission, Captain.
on your project, Doctor.
You new here?
Not exactly.
Come on, you bastard.
Gotcha.
Whew.
(SIGHS)
Back in the game.
HOWARD: Arnim, you in there?
Arnim?
Hey!
The door is this way, pal.
Oh, yeah.
Looking for Doctor Zola,
have you seen him?
Yeah, Doctor Zola.
No, I haven't seen a soul.
Pardon me.
Do I know you?
No, sir. Uh...
I'm a visitor from MIT.
Oh. MIT.
Got a name?
Howard.
- That'll be easy to remember.
- Howard...
Potts.
Well,
I'm Howard Stark.
Hi.
Shake that,
don't pull it.
Yeah.
You look a little green around the
gills, there, Potts.
I'm fine.
Just long hours.
You wanna get some air?
- Hello, Potts.
- Yeah.
- That'd be swell.
- That way.
Okay.
Need your briefcase?
(CHUCKLES)
You're not one of those
beatniks, are you, Potts?
(TELEPHONE RINGING)
- HANK PYM: Hello?
- STEVE: (ON PHONE) Doctor Pym?
HANK PYM: That would be the
number that you called, yes.
This is Captain Stevens
from shipping.
We have a package for you.
Oh, bring it up.
That's the thing, sir,
we can't.
I'm confused.
I thought that was your job.
Well, it's just...
Sir, the box is glowing...
and to be honest,
some of our mail guys
aren't feeling that great.
They didn't open it,
did they?
Uh, yeah, they did.
You better get down here.
Excuse me!
Out of the way!
So, flowers and sauerkraut.
You got a big date tonight?
Uh, my wife's expecting.
And too much time
at the office.
Congratulations.
- Thanks. Hold this, will ya?
- Yeah, sure.
- How far along is she?
- Uh, I don't know.
She's at the point where
she can't stand
the sound of my chewing.
I guess I'll be eating
dinner in the pantry again.
I have a little girl.
A girl would be nice.
Less of a chance she'd
turn out exactly like me.
What'd be so awful
about that?
Let's just say
that the greater good
has rarely outweighed
my own self-interest.
GUARD: And you've never seen
these two men before?
No, I've got an eye for this.
The two of them looked fishy.
Can you describe them?
One of them
had a hippie beard.
GUARD: Hippie.
Like Bee Gees or Mungo Jerry?
FEMALE AGENT:
Definitely Mungo Jerry.
Yeah, this is Chesler.
I need every available MP
to sublevel six.
We have
a potential breach.
PEGGY: I said bring them in.
They're trying, ma'am,
but Braddock's unit
has been stopped
by lightning strikes.
Oh, for the love of...
I'll look at
the weather projections.
(INDISTINCT)
It's not lightning strikes
we're looking at.
TONY: So, where you at
with names?
HOWARD: Well, if it's a boy,
my wife likes Elmonzo.
TONY: Huh. Might wanna
let that stew awhile.
- You got time.
- Uh-huh.
Let me ask you
a question.
When your kid was born,
were you nervous?
- Wildly.
- (SIGHS)
- Yeah.
- Did you feel qualified?
Like you had any idea
how to successfully operate
that thing?
I literally pieced it
together as I went along.
I thought about
what my dad did.
HOWARD: (SIGHS) My old man,
he never met a problem he
couldn't solve with a belt.
I thought my dad
was tough on me.
And now,
looking back on it,
I just remember
the good stuff.
You know? He did drop
the odd pearl.
Yeah? Like what?
"No amount of money ever
bought a second of time."
Smart guy.
He did his best.
I'll tell you,
that kid's not even here yet
and there's nothing
I wouldn't do for him.
Good to meet you, Potts.
Yeah.
Howard...
everything's gonna be
all right.
Thank you...
for everything...
you've done
for this country.
HOWARD: Jarvis.
Have we ever met
that guy?
You meet
a lot of people, sir.
Seems very familiar.
Weird beard.
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING) You're weak.
I'm you.
(GROANS)
(GASPS)
NEBULA:
You could stop this.
You know you want to.
Did you see what happens
in the future?
Thanos finds the Soul Stone.
You wanna know
how he does that?
what he does to you?
That's enough.
- (GRUNTS)
- (NEBULA GROANS)
(NEBULA CHOKES)
You disgust me.
But that doesn't mean
you're useless.
How do I look?
Wow.
Under different
circumstances...
this would be
totally awesome.
NATASHA: (GROANS)
I bet the raccoon
didn't have to climb
a mountain.
Technically he's not
a raccoon, you know?
Oh, whatever.
He eats garbage.
RED SKULL: Welcome.
Natasha.
Daughter of Ivan.
Clint.
Son of Edith.
Who are you?
Consider me a guide...
to you...
and to all who seek
the Soul Stone.
Oh, good.
You tell us where it is,
then we'll be on our way.
(SPEAKS GERMAN)
If only it were that easy.
What you seek
lies in front of you.
As does what you fear.
The stone's down there.
RED SKULL:
For one of you.
For the other...
In order to take
the stone...
you must lose
that which you love.
An everlasting exchange.
A soul for a soul.
BARTON: How's it going?
(CHUCKLES)
Jesus.
Maybe he's making
this shit up.
No.
I don't think so.
Why? 'Cause he knows
your daddy's name?
I didn't.
Thanos left here
with the stone...
without his daughter.
That's not a coincidence.
Yeah.
Whatever it takes.
If we don't get that stone...
billions of people stay dead.
Yeah.
Then I guess we both know
who it's gotta be.
I guess we do.
I'm starting to think
we mean different
people here, Natasha.
For the last five years,
I've been trying to do one thing.
Get to right here.
That's all it's been about.
Bringing everybody back.
No, don't you get
all decent on me now.
What, you think
I wanna do it?
I'm trying to save your life,
you idiot.
Yeah, well, I don't
want you to. How's that?
Natasha, you know
what I've done.
You know what I've become.
Oh, I don't judge people
on their worst mistakes.
Maybe you should.
You didn't.
You're a pain in my ass,
you know that?
Okay.
You win.
(GRUNTING)
Tell my family I love 'em.
You tell 'em yourself.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
Damn you.
(GRUNTS)
Wait.
Let me go.
No.
No. Please, no.
It's okay.
Please.
No!
(PANTING)
(SOBBING)
Did we get 'em all?
Are you telling me
this actually worked?
Clint, where's Nat?
(GASPS SOFTLY)
Do we know
if she had family?
Yeah.
Us.
What?
Huh?
- What are you doing?
- Just asked him a question.
Yeah, no, you're acting
like she's dead.
Why are we acting
like she's dead?
We have the stones, right?
As long as we have
the stones...
Cap, we can bring her back.
Isn't that right?
So, stop this shit. We're the Avengers.
Get it together.
Can't get her back.
What's he...?
What?
It can't be undone.
It can't.
(LAUGHS)
Look, I'm sorry,
no offense,
but you're a very
earthly being, okay?
And we're talking
about space magic.
And "can't" seems very definitive.
Don't you think?
Yeah, look, I know
that I'm way outside
my pay grade here.
But she still
isn't here, is she?
THOR: No, that's my point.
It can't be undone.
Or that's at least
what the red,
floating guy had to say.
Maybe you wanna go
talk to him, okay?
Go grab your hammer and you
go fly and you talk to him.
It was supposed to be me.
She sacrificed her life
for that goddamn stone.
She bet her life on it.
(GRUNTS)
She's not coming back.
We have to make it
worth it.
We have to.
We will.
Boom!
(CHUCKLES MISCHIEVOUSLY)
All right,
the glove's ready.
Question is, who's gonna
snap their freakin' fingers?
- I'll do it.
- TONY: Excuse me?
THOR: It's okay.
TONY: Stop, stop.
Slow down.
Thor. Just wait.
We haven't decided
who's gonna put that on yet.
I'm sorry. What, we're all
just sitting around
waiting for
the right opportunity?
We should at least
discuss it.
Look, sitting here
staring at the thing
is not gonna bring
everybody back.
I'm the strongest Avenger,
okay?
So, this responsibility
falls upon me.
- Normally, you're right.
- It's my duty.
- It's not about that.
- It's not that. (SHUSHES)
- TONY: Hey, buddy...
- Stop it! Just let me.
Just let me do it.
Just let me do something good.
Something right.
Look, it's not
just the fact...
that that glove is channeling
enough energy
to light up a continent.
I'm telling you.
You're in no condition.
What do you think is coursing
through my veins right now?
Cheez Whiz?
Lightning.
Yeah.
SMART HULK:
Lightning won't help you, pal.
It's gotta be me.
You saw what those
stones did to Thanos.
They almost killed him.
None of you could survive.
STEVE: How do we know
you will?
SMART HULK: We don't.
But the radiation's
mostly gamma.
It's like...
I was made for this.
Good to go, yeah?
Let's do it.
Okay, remember,
everyone Thanos snapped away
five years ago...
you're just bringing them
back to now, today.
Don't change anything
from the last five years.
Got it.
IRON MAN:
Friday, do me a favor
and activate Barn Door
Protocol, will ya?
FRIDAY: Yes, boss.
Everybody comes home.
(GROANING)
Take it off! Take it off!
No, wait.
Bruce, are you okay?
- (CONTINUES GROANING)
- IRON MAN: Talk to me, Banner.
I'm okay.
(PANTING HEAVILY)
(YELLING)
(SNAPS)
STEVE: Bruce!
Don't move him.
(GROANING)
(DOORS OPENING)
- Did it work?
- We're not sure. It's okay.
(CELL PHONE VIBRATING)
(BIRDS CHIRPING)
(CELL PHONE
CONTINUES VIBRATING)
Honey.
LAURA: Clint?
Guys...
I think it worked.
(WAR MACHINE YELPING)
I can't breathe!
- (GROANS)
- (RAPID BEEPING)
Canopy, canopy, canopy.
(GRUNTING)
Rhodey, Rocket,
get out of here.
ROCKET: Let me up! Let me up!
Come on!
(RHODES STRAINING)
(EXHALES)
Rhodey!
ROCKET: Huh?
RHODES: Mayday, Mayday!
Does anybody copy?
We're on the lower level.
It's flooding!
ANT-MAN: What? What?
RHODES: We are drowning!
Does anybody copy? Mayday!
ANT-MAN: Wait! I'm here!
I'm here. Can you hear me?
(GRUNTING)
(GROANS)
Cap?
(QUIET GROWL)
Okay.
(CREATURES SNARLING)
Daughter.
Yes, Father.
So, this is the future.
Well done.
Thank you, Father.
They suspected nothing.
The arrogant never do.
Go.
Find the stones,
bring them to me.
What will you do?
Wait.
(WHIRRING)
Tell me something.
In the future...
what happens
to you and me?
I try to kill you.
Several times.
But eventually...
we become friends.
We become sisters.
GAMORA: Come on.
We can stop him.
TONY: Come on, buddy,
wake up!
- (GASPING)
- That's my man.
You lose this again,
I'm keeping it.
What happened?
You mess with time,
it tends to mess back.
You'll see.
(GRUNTS)
What's he been doing?
Absolutely nothing.
STEVE: Where are the stones?
Somewhere under all this.
All I know is
he doesn't have 'em.
So, we keep it that way.
You know
it's a trap, right?
Yeah.
I don't much care.
Good.
Just as long
as we're all in agreement.
(THUNDER CRACKING)
Let's kill him
properly this time.
You could not live
with your own failure.
Where did that bring you?
Back to me.
I thought by eliminating
half of life...
the other half
would thrive.
But you've shown me...
that's impossible.
And as long as there are those
that remember what was...
there will always be those
that are unable to accept
what can be.
They will resist.
Yep, we're all kinds
of stubborn.
I'm thankful.
Because now...
I know what I must do.
I will shred
this universe...
down to its last atom.
And then...
with the stones
you've collected for me...
create a new one...
teeming with life...
that knows not
what it has lost...
but only
what it has been given.
A grateful universe.
Born out of blood.
They'll never know it.
Because you won't be alive
to tell them.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTING)
See you
on the other side, man.
(ROCKET WHIMPERING)
ANT-MAN: Hang on!
I'm coming!
(GRUNTING)
(CREATURES SNARLING)
(BEEPING)
(GRUNTS)
(GROWLING)
Yeah!
(YELLS)
(GRUNTS)
(PANTING)
Oh, hey.
I know you.
Father...
I have the stones.
What?
GAMORA: Stop.
You're betraying us?
You don't have to do this.
I am this.
No, you're not.
You've seen what we become.
Nebula, listen to her.
You can change.
He won't let me.
No!
(GROANS)
Okay, Thor. Hit me.
(YELLING)
(GRUNTS)
FRIDAY: Boss, wake up!
(THOR GRUNTS)
(BOTH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
I knew it!
(THANOS GROANING)
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(THANOS YELLS)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(STRAINING)
In all my years
of conquest...
violence...
slaughter...
it was never personal.
But I'll tell you now...
what I'm about to do
to your stubborn,
annoying little planet...
I'm gonna enjoy it...
very, very much.
(INHALES SHARPLY)
(STRAINED GRUNTING)
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
SAM: (ON SPEAKERS)
Hey, Cap, you read me?
Cap, it's Sam.
Can you hear me?
On your left.
(ALL CHANTING IN XHOSA)
Is that everyone?
What? You wanted more?
(ALL SHOUTING IN UNISON)
CAPTAIN AMERICA: Avengers...
assemble.
(ALL YELLING)
(THOR YELLING)
(ALL SHOUTING)
M'BAKU: Die!
(ALL GRUNTING)
(DRAX YELLING)
No, no, give me that.
You have the little one.
SPIDER-MAN: Hey!
Holy cow!
You will not believe
what's been going on.
Do you remember
when we were in space?
And I got all dusty?
And I must've passed out,
because I woke up
and you were gone.
But Doctor Strange was there,
right? And he was like...
"It's been five years.
Come on, they need us."
And then he started doing
the yellow sparkly thing
- that he does all the time.
- He did? Oh, no.
- What are you doing?
- Oh.
Oh, this is nice.
(QUILL PANTING)
Gamora?
I thought I lost you.
Ow.
- (GROANING)
- Don't touch me!
You missed the first time.
Then you got 'em both
the second time.
GAMORA: This is the one?
Seriously?
Your choices were him
or a tree.
(MOUTHING)
(CREATURE ROARS)
(YELLING)
Cap!
What do you want me to do
with this damn thing?
Get those stones
as far away as possible!
SMART HULK: No!
We need to get 'em back
where they came from.
No way to get 'em back.
Thanos destroyed
the quantum tunnel.
ANT-MAN: Hold on!
That wasn't
our only time machine.
(HORN PLAYS LA CUCARACHA)
Anyone see an ugly brown van
out there?
Yes! But you're not gonna like
where it's parked!
Scott, how long you need
to get that thing working?
Uh, maybe 10 minutes.
Get it started.
We'll get the stones to you.
We're on it, Cap.
TONY: Hey.
You said one out of
14 million, we win, yeah?
Tell me this is it.
If I tell you what happens...
it won't happen.
You better be right.
It's a mess back here.
It's dead.
- What?
- It's dead.
I have to hot-wire it.
Where's Nebula?
She's not responding.
Sire...
(CREATURES SCREECHING)
(GRUNTS)
(CREATURES SNARLING)
BLACK PANTHER: Clint!
Give it to me.
(YELLING)
You took everything from me.
I don't even know
who you are.
You will.
(PANTING)
(GRUNTS)
(BLACK PANTHER YELPING)
SPIDER-MAN: I got it!
Activate Instant Kill.
(GRUNTS)
(GRUNTING)
Rain fire!
But, sire, our troops!
Just do it!
PEPPER: Uh, is anyone else
seeing this?
SPIDER-MAN: I got this!
(GRUNTS) I got this.
Okay, I don't got this.
(OVER SPEAKERS)
Help, somebody help!
Hey, Queens, heads up!
Hang on. I got you, kid.
SPIDER-MAN: Hey!
Nice to meet you...
Oh, my God!
(GRUNTS)
(YELPS)
(GROOT GRUNTS)
(ROCKET YELLING)
(BOTH GASP)
What the hell is this?
Friday,
what are they firing at?
FRIDAY: Something just
entered the upper atmosphere.
(POWERING DOWN)
Oh, yeah!
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Danvers,
we need an assist here.
(BEEPS)
Hi, I'm Peter Parker.
Hey, Peter Parker.
You got something for me?
(GRUNTING)
I don't know how you're gonna
get it through all of that.
Don't worry.
She's got help.
(SCARLET WITCH GRUNTING)
(GRUNTS)
(THOR GRUNTING)
(YELLS)
(THANOS GRUNTS)
(YELLING)
(CAPTAIN MARVEL GRUNTING)
(YELLS, GRUNTS)
(GROANING)
I am inevitable.
(CLANGS)
(WHIRRING)
And I...
(PANTING)
am...
Iron Man.
(SNAPS)
(RUMBLING)
(RUMBLING QUIETS)
(SIGHS)
(GRUNTS)
(EXHALES)
(PANTING)
PETER: Mr. Stark?
Hey! (BREATHING SHAKILY)
Mr. Stark.
Can you hear me?
It's Peter.
Hey.
We won, Mr. Stark.
We won! You did it, sir,
you did it.
(CRYING) I'm sorry.
Tony.
Hey.
(SOFTLY) Hey, Pep.
Friday?
FRIDAY:
Life functions critical.
Tony?
Look at me.
(GROANS WEAKLY)
We're gonna be okay.
(WHEEZING)
You can rest now.
(WHEEZING STOPS)
(SOBBING)
(INAUDIBLE)
TONY: Everybody wants
a happy ending, right?
But it doesn't always
roll that way.
Maybe this time.
I'm hoping
if you play this back...
it's in celebration.
I hope families are reunited.
I hope we get it back.
And something like
a normal version
of the planet
has been restored.
If there ever was
such a thing.
God, what a world.
Universe, now.
If you told me 10 years ago
that we weren't alone...
let alone to this extent,
I mean,
(STAMMERS) I wouldn't have
been surprised...
but come on, who knew?
The epic forces of
darkness and light
that have come into play.
And for better or worse...
that's the reality
Morgan's gonna
have to find a way
to grow up in.
(WHIRRING)
So, I thought I'd probably
better record
a little greeting...
in the case of an untimely death.
On my part.
Not that death at any time
isn't untimely.
This time travel thing
that we're gonna
try and pull off tomorrow...
it's got me
scratching my head
about the survivability
of it all.
That's the thing.
Then again,
that's the hero gig, right?
Part of the journey
is the end.
What am I even tripping for?
Everything is gonna work out
exactly the way
it's supposed to.
I love you 3,000.
(GASPS SOFTLY)
You know,
I wish there was a way
that I could let her know.
That we won.
We did it.
She knows.
They both do.
HAPPY:
How you doing, squirt?
Good.
- You good?
- Mm-hmm.
- Good. You hungry?
What do you want?
Cheeseburgers.
You know, your dad
liked cheeseburgers.
Okay.
I'm gonna get you
all the cheeseburgers
you want.
Okay.
(BIRD CALLING IN DISTANCE)
(BELL CLANGING IN DISTANCE)
(FOOTSTEPS RUSTLING)
VALKYRIE: So...
when can we
expect you back?
(THOR SMACKS LIPS)
Um, about that...
Thor, your people
need a king.
No, they already have one.
(LAUGHS)
That's funny.
Are you being serious?
It's time for me
to be who I am...
rather than
who I'm supposed to be.
But you, you're a leader.
That's who you are.
You know, I'd make
a lot of changes around here.
(CHUCKLES)
I'm counting on it...
Your Majesty.
What will you do?
I'm not sure.
For the first time
in a thousand years,
I have no path.
I do have a ride though.
Move it or lose it,
hairbag.
(THOR CHUCKLES)
THOR: Oh, here we are!
Tree, good to see you.
(GRUNTS)
The Asgardians of the Galaxy
back together again.
Where to first?
Hey.
Just so you know,
this is my ship still.
I'm in charge.
I know. I know.
Of course you are.
Of course.
(BEEPS)
(DRAX CRUNCHING)
See, you say, "Of course,"
but then you touch the map.
It makes you think
that maybe
you didn't realize
I was in charge.
Quail, that's your own
insecurities in there.
Quail?
Okay? I am merely trying
to be of service
and assisting.
Quill.
That's what I said.
You should fight one another
for the honor of leadership.
Sounds fair.
(QUILL STAMMERS)
- It's not necessary, okay?
- It's not.
ROCKET:
I got some blasters,
unless you guys
wanna use knives.
Oh, yes!
Please, use knives.
Yeah. Knives.
I am Groot.
(BOTH LAUGH)
Not necessary.
There shall be
no knifing one another.
Everybody knows
who's in charge.
(THOR SIGHS,
SMACKS LIPS)
Me.
Right?
Yes, you. (LAUGHS)
Of course! Of course.
Of course.
SMART HULK: Remember...
you have to return the stones
to the exact moment
you got 'em...
or you're gonna open up
a bunch of nasty
alternative realities.
Don't worry, Bruce.
Clip all the branches.
You know, I tried.
When I had the gauntlet,
the stones,
I really tried
to bring her back.
I miss her, man.
Me too.
(HELICOPTER WHIRRING)
SAM: You know, if you want,
I could come with you.
You're a good man, Sam.
This one's on me, though.
Don't do anything stupid
till I get back.
How can I?
You're taking
all the stupid with you.
Gonna miss you, buddy.
It's gonna be okay, Buck.
(MACHINE WHIRRING)
How long
is this gonna take?
For him, as long as he needs.
For us, five seconds.
You ready, Cap?
All right, we'll meet you
back here, okay?
You bet.
SMART HULK: Going quantum.
Three...
two...
one.
And returning in five...
four...
three, two...
one.
Where is he?
I don't know. He blew
right by his time stamp.
He should be here.
SAM: Get him back.
- SMART HULK: I'm trying.
- SAM: Get him the hell back.
- Hey, I said I'm trying.
- Sam.
Go ahead.
Cap?
Hi, Sam.
So, did something go wrong
or did something go right?
Well, after I put the stones
back, I thought...
maybe...
I'll try some of that life
Tony was telling me to get.
How'd that work out
for ya?
It was beautiful.
Good. I'm happy for you.
Truly.
Thank you.
Only thing
bumming me out...
is the fact I have
to live in a world
without Captain America.
STEVE: Oh.
That reminds me.
Try it on.
How does it feel?
Like it's someone else's.
It isn't.
(SIGHS)
Thank you.
I'll do my best.
That's why it's yours.
You wanna tell me
about her?
No.
No, I don't think I will.
(OLD JAZZ SONG PLAYING)
(OLD JAZZ SONG
CONTINUES PLAYING)
Subtitles by explosiveskull
www.OpenSubtitles.org
(METAL CLANGING)